module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Where is the most popular spot to commit suicide in the United States?', 
    a: 'Empire State Building',
    b: 'Sears Tower',
    c: 'Golden Gate Bridge',
    d: 'Coronado Bridge',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where would you be most likely to see a "widow\'s peak"?', 
    a: 'On the Human Head',
    b: 'In the Rocky Mountains',
    c: 'At a Motorsport Event',
    d: 'In a Cemetery',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which author was a close friend of J.R.R. Tolkien?', 
    a: 'Ian Fleming',
    b: 'EM Forster',
    c: 'Walter de la Mare',
    d: 'C S Lewis',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What sort of stylistic device is "forward retreat"?', 
    a: 'oxymoron',
    b: 'tautology',
    c: 'alliteration',
    d: 'personification',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does a fletcher make?', 
    a: 'Barrels',
    b: 'Arrows',
    c: 'Pottery',
    d: 'Cutlery',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city did the infamous Jack the Ripper roam?', 
    a: 'London',
    b: 'York',
    c: 'Dublin',
    d: 'Manchester',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is oolong?', 
    a: 'A type of Tea',
    b: 'A variety of Verjuice',
    c: 'A kind of Coffee',
    d: 'A sort of Saki',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'How did Sonny Bono die?', 
    a: 'Skiing Accident',
    b: 'Overdose',
    c: 'Heart attack',
    d: 'Suicide',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The human coccyx can be compared to what in other animals?', 
    a: 'Claws',
    b: 'Multiple Nipples',
    c: 'Tail',
    d: 'Snout',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the dot of an i or j called?', 
    a: 'tittle',
    b: 'dot',
    c: 'spec',
    d: 'umlaut',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];